<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Thread Recap</title>
    <link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Thread Recap</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 2020 Set 2</title>
      <link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2020-03-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2020-03-30/</guid>
      <description>Mar 2020 Set 2
Jobbo_Fett    Incredifun is the dumbest thing I&amp;rsquo;ve heard all week.
   Sorry, it is IncredifFUD.
   Has anyone said Fart Poopizen yet
 The Titanic   I’m honestly shocked that CIG haven’t pulled the COVID-19 card yet, it would be the perfect excuse to kick the SQ42 can down the road for at least
a few months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mar 2020 Set 1</title>
      <link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2020-03-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2020-03-15/</guid>
      <description>Mar 2020 Set 1
  https://www.millenium.org/news/360471.html
Star Citizen : Interview de Dan Trufin au Bar Citizen de Liège 2020  According to Dan, refueling is more an activity than a full career. This involves buying fuel (or making it), possibly responding to a distress call, and transferring fuel from one vessel to another.
Chris Robert wants the connection between the ships to be visible . There will therefore be a pole as for supply planes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feb 2020 Set 1</title>
      <link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2020-02-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2020-02-15/</guid>
      <description>Feb 2020 Set 1
  When does Star Citizen 2 come out
 Roadmap TheAgent   Zero roadmap updates this week.
Holy. Hell.
 no mr calder, mr roberts isn&amp;rsquo;t in, no no I swear he&amp;rsquo;s not standing next to me frantically waving his arms and mouthing I&amp;rsquo;M NOT HERE and he&amp;rsquo;s not getting into his porche and peeling out of the parking lot. can I take a message?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 2020 Set 2</title>
      <link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2020-01-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2020-01-31/</guid>
      <description>January 2020 Set 2
Jan Set 2 - 2020
   [PTU Bug Hunt] 30009 or 30006 errors.
Discussion
January 21st at 6:48 am
Greetings!
We need help tracking down another issue. The 3k9 or 3k6 errors are fairly common on live, are often associated with recovery and/or bed logout, and can be debilitating. However, due to account copy they frequently are under reported during the PTU cycle. If any of you experienced this issue, please post below and let us know if/how you were able to resolve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 2020 Set 2</title>
      <link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2020-01-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2020-01-15/</guid>
      <description>January 2020 Set 2
    LMAO! Sorry none of this janky shit works after almost a decade, so here have a janky ass jpeg to look at.
   the ship is the fix
  they&amp;rsquo;re giving you a ship because it&amp;rsquo;s the only way to get past the fucking issue
   What in the world is so wrong with this game that a fix is to log into an entirely different game mode and lay down in a bed?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 2019 Set 2</title>
      <link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-12-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-12-31/</guid>
      <description>December 2019 Set 2
Squadron 42: 2019 Visual Teaser
  Ship assets on a pretty background.
Gameplay not included.
Merry Christmas, bring money.
    Zero examples of a functioning game or story, but hey there are some scenery renders.
 CIG&amp;rsquo;s development in a nutshell.
   spinning models in a model viewer seems like the most perfect way to represent the state of the project and its future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 2019 Set 1</title>
      <link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-12-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-12-15/</guid>
      <description>December 2019 Set 1
       What has really amazed me over the past year or so, is just how openly contemptuous of the backers everyone at CIG has become. Jared will laugh on camera at their expectations of a finished game in a less than geological timescale, Sandi doesn’t even bother to show up and half-ass justify her huge paycheck, and Chris mostly stays in hiding now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>November 2019 Set 2</title>
      <link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-11-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-11-28/</guid>
      <description>November 2019 Set 2
  You don&amp;rsquo;t license an engine when you build an MMO. You especially do not license an engine when building an MMO that is supposed to be the world&amp;rsquo;s first AAAA game and will do things MMOs have never managed to achieve.
They have to build their own engine. Period. There&amp;rsquo;s no other way around it. Buying an engine is a waste of money because you&amp;rsquo;re going to throw it all out and start over anyways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>November 2019 Set 1</title>
      <link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-11-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-11-15/</guid>
      <description>November 2019 Set 1
  Secret build looking huge and good. When it will enter the pipelines the video game world gonna stagger.
 I opened my Star Citizen account 6 1&amp;frasl;2 years ago. You plan on giving me 1&amp;frasl;3 of the game I was promised over a year from now. If we don&amp;rsquo;t get the ENTIRE game we were promises, I will be suing you into oblivion!!! And I will be one among many!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October 2019 Set 2</title>
      <link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-10-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-10-31/</guid>
      <description>October 2019 Set 2
  This game would be fucking awesome if it wasn&amp;rsquo;t such shit!
At this point I&amp;rsquo;m just loosing my mind, bcs I see on reddit and the RSI site that this is a bug that persists for more than a year
   COVALEX SHIPPING KIOSK SPAWNING RANDOM BOXES
     NPCS GET STUCK IN PORT OLISAR
 Talk about putting the game&amp;rsquo;s bugs on display…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October 2019 Set 1</title>
      <link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-10-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-10-18/</guid>
      <description>October 2019 Set 1
Bootcha       wunderbar
     Bootcha just converted A Commando:
  After this video i can only say one thing. This thing really turned into a scam. Maybe not as big as some people make it out to be. But this shit alone proves it and if someone can deny it or some up with a valid factual counter argument please be me guest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September 2019 Set 2</title>
      <link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-09-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-09-30/</guid>
      <description>September 2019 Set 2
Bootcha  Hey gang.
So here&amp;rsquo;s a question.
Espresso Machine cost about $17,000.
Space Door cost about $40,000.
What single, used-once item would cost $100,000?
You&amp;rsquo;ve seen it. You&amp;rsquo;ve absolutely fucking seen it.
Aussies, you&amp;rsquo;ve absolutely fucking seen it.
 Bootcha   Surely not that weird outfit Sandi wore during the presentation in Pax Australia?
 What does your heart tell you?
   I can only assume that it&amp;rsquo;s the complete ensemble;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September 2019 Set 1</title>
      <link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-09-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-09-17/</guid>
      <description>September 2019 Set 1
  I think there&amp;rsquo;s 2 crowds on the SC subreddit - one that is all TRUE BELIEVERS that just post screenshots and praise CIG all day, and people just checking in on the development who are much more realistic. The former isn&amp;rsquo;t even posting in the roadmap threads, and the latter only post when there is development news. So when the sub goes back into fan mode, it&amp;rsquo;s just business as usual and the same people continuing to post what they&amp;rsquo;ve always posted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019 August Set 2</title>
      <link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-08-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-08-31/</guid>
      <description>2019 - August Set 2
Space Court lurches forward
       Crytek put up the cash. Guess they must think they have a shot. Should be interesting at least.
   Crytek putting their life savings on 0 at the roulette table.
   I spent the last 5 hours trying to play Star Citizen.
I probably won&amp;rsquo;t log back on. Convince me otherwise?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>November Set 1</title>
      <link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-11-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-11-08/</guid>
      <description>November Set 1
  VictorianQueerLit  I think the best part of the Star Citizen Scam finally collapsing is that a large number of nerds will stop psychotically obsessing over Elite Dangerous being THE ENEMY and instead maybe shut up and enjoy the game that delivers on many of Chris Roberts promises.
I&amp;rsquo;m sure there will always be people that refuse to play it because it dared to exist opposite of Star Citizen and ten years from now at any mention of Elite Dangerous they will scoff and go into a rage filled tirade about &amp;ldquo;Polygon Tacos&amp;rdquo; or whatever but I think that will be a small minority.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All Time Greatest Posts</title>
      <link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-10-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-10-10/</guid>
      <description>All Time Greatest Posts
Reserved for all time greatest posts
        The one thing we should have learned by now is that time and Star Citizen makes fools of us all. The SC faithful have been so sure that total success is just around the corner for so long. And the SC skeptics have been so sure that total collapse has been just around the corner for so long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017 August Set 1</title>
      <link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-08-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-08-10/</guid>
      <description>2017 - August Set 1
G0RF  &amp;ldquo;Soon there will be a jump gate that can take me to the Helios system! I bet we&amp;rsquo;ll have underwater vehicles by then and I can explore the vast depths of Helios II! I&amp;rsquo;m going to set up deep sea mining operations as soon as its live so I can get a head start carving out my thrilling future as an Oceanic Mining Tycoon!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>