<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Priceless Trainwreck</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Priceless Trainwreck</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>April 2025</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2025-04-30/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2025-04-30/</guid><description>It appears the pledge counter has reached the $800m milestone. It should only be $798m because of the missing the $2m but we won&amp;rsquo;t worry about that, no one else does.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the rest of the story though. I&amp;rsquo;ve used end of March 2025. Technically you could say they have raised over $1b but since they returned $4.8m to investors by way of dividend and I&amp;rsquo;ve deducted that from the capital raise, so the receipts side of the business is only actually $995m.</description></item><item><title>March 2025</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2025-03-31/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2025-03-31/</guid><description>Star Citizen should have exclusive Concierge-only servers.
anything funny happening in the world of star citizen?
A quick google suggest Star Citizen still exists.
That&amp;rsquo;s sorta funny.
Majority of the complaints are from people who don&amp;rsquo;t play the game.
It&amp;rsquo;s also alpha – these things will happen. I always mention to people if they are unwilling to deal with the alpha woes, they need to stick with something else until Star Citizen enter beta.</description></item><item><title>February 2025</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2025-02-25/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2025-02-25/</guid><description>Breaking news: Star citizen concierge+ backer confirms Derek Smart was right Actually really intresting video, Camural has always been pretty open about criticizing CIG but I&amp;rsquo;ve never a creator so invested in SC&amp;rsquo;s success be quite this disillusioned before. Also very happy that the legacy of uncle Derek still lives on in backers minds!
Bonus pic:
I think is likely to happen, funding will drop for a few months and CIG will finally relent and remove Master Modes (CIGs latest flight model that is hated by Citizens) and this will be seen as CIG listening to the community and a flood of sales will return.</description></item><item><title>January 2025</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2025-01-31/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2025-01-31/</guid><description>Star Engine Chris Roberts Space Game Engine
10&amp;rsquo;s of thousands of players in a single instance
60 FPS twitch shooter
Realistic physics and fluid simulations
Fully realistic flight model with ship components and damage modelling
Oh and ground vehicles too
Every object is permanent and tracked by servers forever (coffee cup in the woods)
yeah seems easy enough
You forgot the Argon Levels
Fully simulated NPC populations on a global scale, 10:1 NPC:Player</description></item><item><title>December 2024</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2024-12-24/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2024-12-24/</guid><description>December 2024
I don&amp;rsquo;t think there was an ELE, but i do think CIG has been mortally wounded by 1000 self-inflicted cuts (and counting) over 2024. We&amp;rsquo;ll probably know by next week how dire the situation is. I&amp;rsquo;m not saying &amp;ldquo;90 days tops,&amp;rdquo; but the next few days are critical for Parp Citizen. Poor IAE sales could induce an unrecoverable flat spin.The passengers and crew of UEE Only Constant are justifiably nervous and upset.</description></item><item><title>October 2024</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2024-10-01/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2024-10-01/</guid><description>October 2024
CIG Enters Crunch Time INSIDER GAMING: Star Citizen Developer Cloud Imperium Games Imposes 7-Day Work Week Ahead of Citizencon
An internal email sent to staff yesterday states that the company needs to “double down over the next 18 days to make sure that once again we create an amazing experience for our community.” This includes finalizing patch 3.24.2 for Star Citizen and having a Squadron 42 demo showcase for Chapter 1.</description></item><item><title>January 2024</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2024-01-01/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2024-01-01/</guid><description>January 2024
This week I’ve accumulated over 5000 in pledges.
I kinda wish this was a joke but I have a genuine addiction.
I have no idea what I’m doing.
Please help.
My girlfriend is pissed about how much I spent on ships this week she said she may actually leave and went back to her parents. I had to tell her I ruined my credit and we can’t get a new apartment this year till I fix it</description></item><item><title>April 2020 Set 2</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2020-04-22/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2020-04-22/</guid><description>April 2020 Set 2
It&amp;rsquo;s fun watching rationalanthropoid&amp;rsquo;s arguments over at devolve into huge walls of text about how CIG sucks at communicating their progress but is also progressing really well, although we cannot really observe that so we must extrapolate the truth based on how much they suck at communicating.
So, since they suck so much at that then what they are truly saying can be anything and therefore it is!</description></item><item><title>Mar 2020 Set 2</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2020-03-30/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2020-03-30/</guid><description>Mar 2020 Set 2
Incredifun is the dumbest thing I&amp;rsquo;ve heard all week.
Sorry, it is IncredifFUD.
Has anyone said Fart Poopizen yet
I’m honestly shocked that CIG haven’t pulled the COVID-19 card yet, it would be the perfect excuse to kick the SQ42 can down the road for at least
a few months.
You got to wait for the videos to cycle in.</description></item><item><title>Mar 2020 Set 1</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2020-03-15/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2020-03-15/</guid><description>Mar 2020 Set 1
https://www.millenium.org/news/360471.html
Star Citizen : Interview de Dan Trufin au Bar Citizen de Liège 2020 According to Dan, refueling is more an activity than a full career. This involves buying fuel (or making it), possibly responding to a distress call, and transferring fuel from one vessel to another.
Chris Robert wants the connection between the ships to be visible . There will therefore be a pole as for supply planes.</description></item><item><title>Feb 2020 Set 1</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2020-02-15/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2020-02-15/</guid><description>Feb 2020 Set 1
When does Star Citizen 2 come out
Roadmap Zero roadmap updates this week.
Holy. Hell.
no mr calder, mr roberts isn&amp;rsquo;t in, no no I swear he&amp;rsquo;s not standing next to me frantically waving his arms and mouthing I&amp;rsquo;M NOT HERE and he&amp;rsquo;s not getting into his porche and peeling out of the parking lot. can I take a message?</description></item><item><title>January 2020 Set 2</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2020-01-31/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2020-01-31/</guid><description>January 2020 Set 2
Jan Set 2 - 2020
[PTU Bug Hunt] 30009 or 30006 errors.
Discussion
January 21st at 6:48 am
Greetings!
We need help tracking down another issue. The 3k9 or 3k6 errors are fairly common on live, are often associated with recovery and/or bed logout, and can be debilitating. However, due to account copy they frequently are under reported during the PTU cycle. If any of you experienced this issue, please post below and let us know if/how you were able to resolve.</description></item><item><title>January 2020 Set 2</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2020-01-15/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2020-01-15/</guid><description>January 2020 Set 2
LMAO! Sorry none of this janky shit works after almost a decade, so here have a janky ass jpeg to look at.
the ship is the fix
they&amp;rsquo;re giving you a ship because it&amp;rsquo;s the only way to get past the fucking issue
What in the world is so wrong with this game that a fix is to log into an entirely different game mode and lay down in a bed?</description></item><item><title>December 2019 Set 2</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-12-31/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-12-31/</guid><description>December 2019 Set 2
Squadron 42: 2019 Visual Teaser
Ship assets on a pretty background.
Gameplay not included.
Merry Christmas, bring money.
Zero examples of a functioning game or story, but hey there are some scenery renders.
CIG&amp;rsquo;s development in a nutshell.
spinning models in a model viewer seems like the most perfect way to represent the state of the project and its future.</description></item><item><title>December 2019 Set 1</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-12-15/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-12-15/</guid><description>December 2019 Set 1
What has really amazed me over the past year or so, is just how openly contemptuous of the backers everyone at CIG has become. Jared will laugh on camera at their expectations of a finished game in a less than geological timescale, Sandi doesn’t even bother to show up and half-ass justify her huge paycheck, and Chris mostly stays in hiding now.</description></item><item><title>November 2019 Set 2</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-11-28/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-11-28/</guid><description>November 2019 Set 2
You don&amp;rsquo;t license an engine when you build an MMO. You especially do not license an engine when building an MMO that is supposed to be the world&amp;rsquo;s first AAAA game and will do things MMOs have never managed to achieve.
They have to build their own engine. Period. There&amp;rsquo;s no other way around it. Buying an engine is a waste of money because you&amp;rsquo;re going to throw it all out and start over anyways.</description></item><item><title>November 2019 Set 1</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-11-15/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-11-15/</guid><description>November 2019 Set 1
Secret build looking huge and good. When it will enter the pipelines the video game world gonna stagger.
I opened my Star Citizen account 6 1&amp;frasl;2 years ago. You plan on giving me 1&amp;frasl;3 of the game I was promised over a year from now. If we don&amp;rsquo;t get the ENTIRE game we were promises, I will be suing you into oblivion!!! And I will be one among many!</description></item><item><title>October 2019 Set 2</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-10-31/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-10-31/</guid><description>October 2019 Set 2
This game would be fucking awesome if it wasn&amp;rsquo;t such shit!
At this point I&amp;rsquo;m just loosing my mind, bcs I see on reddit and the RSI site that this is a bug that persists for more than a year
COVALEX SHIPPING KIOSK SPAWNING RANDOM BOXES
NPCS GET STUCK IN PORT OLISAR
Talk about putting the game&amp;rsquo;s bugs on display…</description></item><item><title>October 2019 Set 1</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-10-18/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-10-18/</guid><description>October 2019 Set 1
wunderbar
Bootcha just converted A Commando:
After this video i can only say one thing. This thing really turned into a scam. Maybe not as big as some people make it out to be. But this shit alone proves it and if someone can deny it or some up with a valid factual counter argument please be me guest.</description></item><item><title>September 2019 Set 2</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-09-30/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-09-30/</guid><description>September 2019 Set 2
Hey gang.
So here&amp;rsquo;s a question.
Espresso Machine cost about $17,000.
Space Door cost about $40,000.
What single, used-once item would cost $100,000?
You&amp;rsquo;ve seen it. You&amp;rsquo;ve absolutely fucking seen it.
Aussies, you&amp;rsquo;ve absolutely fucking seen it.
Surely not that weird outfit Sandi wore during the presentation in Pax Australia?
What does your heart tell you?
I can only assume that it&amp;rsquo;s the complete ensemble;</description></item><item><title>September 2019 Set 1</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-09-17/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-09-17/</guid><description>September 2019 Set 1
I think there&amp;rsquo;s 2 crowds on the SC subreddit - one that is all TRUE BELIEVERS that just post screenshots and praise CIG all day, and people just checking in on the development who are much more realistic. The former isn&amp;rsquo;t even posting in the roadmap threads, and the latter only post when there is development news. So when the sub goes back into fan mode, it&amp;rsquo;s just business as usual and the same people continuing to post what they&amp;rsquo;ve always posted.</description></item><item><title>2019 August Set 2</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-08-31/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2019-08-31/</guid><description>2019 - August Set 2
Space Court lurches forward
Crytek put up the cash. Guess they must think they have a shot. Should be interesting at least.
Crytek putting their life savings on 0 at the roulette table.
I spent the last 5 hours trying to play Star Citizen.
I probably won&amp;rsquo;t log back on. Convince me otherwise? That was hell, it was the worst experience in any project I have ever had even tho some of the visuals were stunning.</description></item><item><title>March Set 9</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-03-26/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-03-26/</guid><description>March Set 9
Beer4theBeerGod So that reclaimer ship is playable, for some people I guess. Walkthrough/verbal fellation video here. Kind of looks like they&amp;rsquo;ve hacked it into the arena commander map instead of loading it in the main game. Commentary below:
0:44- So about half of the ship is the landing gear. Deploying it immediately breaks the particle effects on the engines.
1:27- Oh they&amp;rsquo;ve started adding &amp;ldquo;Auto-turrets&amp;rdquo; since it became apparent that nobody will ever crew turrets on their ships.</description></item><item><title>March Set 8</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-03-24/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-03-24/</guid><description>March Set 8
3.1 released to PTU
https://pastebin.com/QH9QScsH
I agree with CIG&amp;rsquo;s assessment to get the patch out by the deadline at all costs. It looks like shit to us, but to backers CIG is turning it around. Delays have been the number one morale killer. If they delayed the first patch of their new quarterly release schedule, it would kill the enthusiasm for questioning backers.</description></item><item><title>March Set 7</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-03-20/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-03-20/</guid><description>March Set 7
Which of the following is more depressing?
CIG set out to perpetrate a scam.
CIG did not set out to perpetrate a scam but once they stumbled into one decided “fuck” it and leaned in?
CIG did not set out to perpetrate a scam but found themselves holding a tiger by the tail and have no idea how to get out of this. So they are just pulling more and more money to forestall the day of reckoning.</description></item><item><title>March Set 6</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-03-16/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-03-16/</guid><description>March Set 6
Rule Change Recommendation - No Concern Trolling
So you’re saying that me reading and commenting in a subreddit I’m subscribed to is the product of some kind of collusion because I like to talk with other people on other mediums? Or are you accusing me directly of all that other stuff?
If you could please elaborate on this extensive coordinated campaign you believe is going on it would help me know how hard to laugh at you.</description></item><item><title>March Set 4</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-03-12/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-03-12/</guid><description>March Set 4
CIG files for protective order
This is some sort of court agreement that would protect certain things from being discovered.
Documents:
NOTICE OF MOTION AND MOTION for Protective Order for CONTROLLING TIMING AND SCOPE OF DISCOVERY PENDING RESOLUTION OF MOTION TO DISMISS
Att: 1 Memorandum OF POINTS AND AUTHORITIES IN SUPPORT OF MOTION FOR PROTECTIVE ORDER,
Att: 2 Declaration OF JEREMY GOLDMAN IN SUPPORT OF MOTION FOR PROTECTIVE ORDER,</description></item><item><title>March Set 3</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-03-10/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-03-10/</guid><description>March Set 3
Seemingly former Star Citizen stream DeejayKnight is now doing something cool and good by streaming with FIRST Robotics Competition. I volunteer for FIRST. It&amp;rsquo;s a lot of fun.
We&amp;rsquo;re seeing a lot more Star Citizen fans and streamers quietly slip away lately. The ones that are left are becoming increasingly agitated and perturbed. Eventually the Brown Sea will be distilled down to a single fan, a single solitary drop of pure rage certain that Star Citizen is coming soon.</description></item><item><title>March Set 2</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-03-08/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-03-08/</guid><description>March Set 2
Sterling has been told for years he should cover the project and has so long ignored it, though he was a natural guy for the job. But I expect he’s getting pinged a lot more now and will see the traction Bootcha’s increasingly getting, he will be dizzied and intimidated by the material already being collated into critique, will let out a big whiny sigh and be finally prompted to summon his schtick and shine his spotlight on the project in the not too distant future.</description></item><item><title>March Set 1</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-03-03/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-03-03/</guid><description>March Set 1
Sunk Cost Galaxy is back baby!
I am not a lawyer.
Worth Clicking: (video: Sunk Cost Galaxy - Chapter 4: The Ecstasy of JPEGs)
I am a broken, mouth-breathing, obsessive troll with nothing better to do than make my opinion heard
here&amp;rsquo;s the calendar from the video: https://i.imgur.com/I7CQWnm.png
Green line was the initial crowdfunding drive.
Red lines are for any time &amp;ldquo;something is on sale&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title>February Set 9</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-02-28/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-02-28/</guid><description>February Set 9
Crytek GmbH v. Cloud Imperium Games Corp Discovery Plan
Crytek&amp;rsquo;s Position:
The primary issues in this case are (i) whether the Defendants breached the Game License Agreement; whether Defendants infringed upon Crytek&amp;rsquo;s copyrighted work; and the amount of damages to which Crytek may be entitled
Defendants&amp;rsquo; Position:
CIG and Crytek entered into a binding and enforceable GLA under which CIG
has fully performed. The threshold legal issue is for Crytek to articulate, in a manner</description></item><item><title>February Set 8</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-02-27/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-02-27/</guid><description>February Set 8
Status of bind culling continues to frustrate backers I feel like this is probably how the year will be shaping up. Quarterly releases, but with everything substantial gradually moving one patch along until it all piles up into one big dump at the end of the year.
So basically the same as last year, only this time instead of pretending there&amp;rsquo;s going to be one big update that continually fails to appear, we now have four smaller patches that will appear but fail to have anything in them.</description></item><item><title>February Set 7</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-02-26/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-02-26/</guid><description>February Set 7
Any word on why Bootcha stopped uploading videos?
I don&amp;rsquo;t know if this is an answer.
Worth Clicking: (video: Sunk Cost Galaxy Interlude 1: Salt Cook Travesty)
In this latest #StarCitizen Blog post, I discuss how role-playing and the game work together to create an immersive world. Full of consequences for actions. A butterfly effect that benefits every player. Thanks for the shoutout @RobertsSpaceInd https://t.</description></item><item><title>February Set 6</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-02-23/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-02-23/</guid><description>February Set 6
YOUTUBE: Calling All Devs
1 - “When will Persistence log us back in to the last place we logged out of?” Chad McKinney (who seems like a cool guy) explains that it formerly did work via a Rube Goldberg machine of code but several changes to Persistence broke it and it will need to be re-fixed. McKinney says the fix will come by 3.1, yet in the wrap-up Lando — sensing the obvious, terrifying threat of unambiguous commitments to fix that which formerly worked via the next patch — helpfully corrects him, saying “You said it will definitely be in by 3.</description></item><item><title>February Set 5</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-02-22/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-02-22/</guid><description>February Set 5
The Road To Eternity team on team size:
&amp;ldquo;We try to keep the team as small as possible, figure it out first. Then once we enter production we can add more people to the team.&amp;rdquo;
CIG on team size in (2014):
If anything you can say Chris has kickstarted a small economy with the number of people and talent he is hiring not to mention the equipment and facilities he is also having to buy/rent/lease.</description></item><item><title>February Set 4</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-02-20/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-02-20/</guid><description>February Set 4
Regarding the beautiful forests in Kingdom Come Deliverance:
They did the same with the Nemesis system from Mordor. Chris Roberts says &amp;ldquo;Oh we&amp;rsquo;ll have that but it&amp;rsquo;ll be even better&amp;rdquo; without any concept or thought into what it involves or the amount of work the programmers and designers went in to making it and balancing it…No, just a simple thing for the fans to go &amp;ldquo;Oh we&amp;rsquo;ll have this as well!</description></item><item><title>February Set 3</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-02-16/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-02-16/</guid><description>February Set 3
each lot is around $85. I mean holy shit. holy fucking shit that&amp;rsquo;s almost $45,000 in housing. the estimated total spend for him on Shroud of the Avatar is something like $100,000 to $125,000 and he&amp;rsquo;s just now complaining about p2w mechanics, lol
the icing on this is his burning hatred of wow, a game which he never played and is about 21398103109283 billion times better than shroud in every single possible way</description></item><item><title>February 9th Anticipation Station</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-02-08/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-02-08/</guid><description>February 9th Anticipation Station
CIG Responds to Crytek&#39;s Response Very boring document: https://www.scribd.com/document/370105345/031127439162
Annoying effort legal post incoming!
The motion will get denied, as it is being filed under FRCP 12(b)6. This particular rule in the charming Federal Rules of Civil Procedure handbook states that a motion can be filed in defense &amp;ldquo;for failure to state a claim for which relief can be granted.&amp;rdquo; This denial is indisputable and inarguable because the standard for a dismissal under FRCP rule 12(b)6 is &amp;ldquo;In appraising the sufficiency of a complaint for failure to state a claim is that a complaint should not be dismissed …unless it appears beyond doubt that the plaintiff can prove no set of facts in support of his claim which would entitle him to relief.</description></item><item><title>February Set 2</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-02-07/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-02-07/</guid><description>February Set 2
hello
I am not discussing the ongoing legal battle. I will not and won&amp;rsquo;t ever utter a word about that. What I will talk about is scope and it&amp;rsquo;s ongoing reduction; something our backers should know and understand now, and not when it suddenly confronts them.
I want to discuss the often quoted &amp;ldquo;game development,&amp;rdquo; specifically when I see our backers pair this with &amp;ldquo;you don&amp;rsquo;t understand.</description></item><item><title>February Set 1</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-02-01/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-02-01/</guid><description>February Set 1
(tweet: Elite: Dangerous Twitter - People playing the game and doing things together. Star Citizen Twitter - Twitch streamers giving away ships, ship raffle entries.)
I mean c&amp;rsquo;mon charlie, even chat doesn&amp;rsquo;t fucking work in star citizen
what else do you expect them to do
The only bug-free program is one with zero lines of code.</description></item><item><title>G 0 RF Interlude 1</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-01-31/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-01-31/</guid><description>G0RF Interlude 1
Read the first post in its entirety, skim the rest as needed.
As far as ship sales and chris roberts goes i’d make the argument that a lot of what we’ve seen so far is the results of attempting to make a game in technologically uncharted territory and announcing it the day development starts.
I think the biggest reason we’ve only seen ship sale after ship sale is due to how damned ridiculous the technological requirement of this project are, and how little they have had to build off of.</description></item><item><title>January Set 12</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-01-30/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-01-30/</guid><description>January Set 12
CIG employee slips persistence misadventure &amp;ldquo;Stolen ships, no matter how well the theft, will not be a long-term thing. You get to enjoy them for the session, but those ships will not be returning when you log back in. Stealing ships should be a short-term goal. Joyriding, piracy or selling them for scrap, not for growing your own fleet.&amp;rdquo;
The gradual walking back of promised features and gameplay continues:</description></item><item><title>January 2018 Set 11</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-01-28/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-01-28/</guid><description>January 2018 Set 11
I just had a summons for jury duty in march
if I somehow end up on the skadden / fkks jury selection, my life will finally be complete
There are so many vectors converging on that single point in time known as the Collapse of Star Citizen that it&amp;rsquo;s nearly impossible to track them all, but here you touch on two of them:</description></item><item><title>January Set 10</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-01-26/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-01-26/</guid><description>January Set 10
https://robertsspaceindustries.com/comm-link/transmission/15666-Bugsmashers
At 2:25 there&amp;rsquo;s some code on screen, which looks very much like CryEngine code and not Lumberyard. CE uses scaleform UI, which is basically flash. LY does not have this, does not come with a scaleform license, and uses a different UI system. So 2.6 was CryEngine, and not Lumberyard. The switch never happened. Called it. They just cherrypicked network stuff from LY onto their codebase, keeping CE specific stuff, essentially still being CryEngine.</description></item><item><title>January Set 9</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-01-24/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-01-24/</guid><description>January Set 9
Defendants&amp;rsquo; Motion seeking dismissal and other relief is without merit: http://docdro.id/v7yQ0LL
RSI: You can&amp;rsquo;t sue us because it was CIG who signed your stupid deal! Skadden:
3. If RSI Is Not A Party To The GLA, Then Crytek&amp;rsquo;s Claims For Copyright Infringement Are Even Stronger:
Defendants&amp;rsquo; suggestion that RSI is not bound by the GLA igores the implications that holding would have for Crytek&amp;rsquo;s claims of copyright infringement.</description></item><item><title>January Set 8</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-01-20/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-01-20/</guid><description>January Set 8
Thanks for this suggestion who-ever it was (I think it was Gorf)
from left to right Sean tracy, Calix Reneau, Tony Z, The Crobbles, The succubus, Matt Sherman, Dave Haddock
The best thing is that it seems like SCs worst enemy has always been SC. Nobody knows what’s happening, and nobody seems to actually be thinking about these things. It’s a lot of times like the first time they’ve heard some of these questions, even after they were probably vetted out for being answered.</description></item><item><title>January Set 5</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-01-15/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-01-15/</guid><description>January Set 5
The last time OSC was posting heavily and backers were enraged I requested an alt check because there were enough discrepancies between the post styles I figured it was a pretty safe bet they weren&amp;rsquo;t the same guy. Of course if I was wrong it would have been a blue on blue incident to rival that of Leonard Skinly, but that&amp;rsquo;s just more lols for the thread.</description></item><item><title>January Set 6</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-01-14/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-01-14/</guid><description>January Set 6
Star Citizen is inexcusable at any stage of development.
I think people willfully miss the point that &amp;ldquo;pre-alpha&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;alpha&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;beta&amp;rdquo;, etc. are just labels. Even though they have fairly normalized use in the software development world, there is no governing authority for their use, so you can claim your &amp;ldquo;game&amp;rdquo; is in whatever stage you feel like calling it. So that&amp;rsquo;s one aspect - that calling it &amp;ldquo;alpha&amp;rdquo; doesn&amp;rsquo;t really mean anything.</description></item><item><title>January Set 4</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-01-09/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-01-09/</guid><description>January Set 4
AtV was all about a preview for the new website they are making In just a little over five years Cloud Imperium Games have created 1,016 youtube videos, 4 websites and 0 games.
&amp;ldquo;People are catching on that we&amp;rsquo;re fudging the funding tracker to bolster backer confidence! But we can&amp;rsquo;t remove it without arousing suspicion. What if we redid the whole website and omitted the tracker?</description></item><item><title>January Set 3</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-01-08/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-01-08/</guid><description>January Set 3
CIG responds to CryTek complaint 13 pdf response: https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1mPjfXrjAf9RUq3_5cJgd-hF-I5XoCQta
Leonard French discussion of response: Legal docs (not doxx), grab them while they&amp;rsquo;re hot. Includes CIG&amp;rsquo;s response, a motion to dismiss, and a copy of the GLA.
https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1mPjfXrjAf9RUq3_5cJgd-hF-I5XoCQta
Comedy addendum: they really did invoke the &amp;ldquo;wrong company&amp;rdquo; defense.
This is the first time we expected something in 2 weeks and CIG delivered early!</description></item><item><title>January Set 2</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-01-07/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-01-07/</guid><description>January Set 2
https://www.twitch.tv/videos/215061920?t=01h19m53s (video: In today&amp;rsquo;s exciting episode, Twerk17 talks about how Electronic Arts is more accountable than CIG)
https://www.twitch.tv/videos/215061920?t=01h33m00s (video: WTFo&amp;rsquo;s poll estimates SC release in 2022)
I listened to this for a minute or two and that bald dickhead went and said that if Star Citizen lives up to 20% of the hype it has built up, it would still be one of the best games ever…</description></item><item><title>January Set 1</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-01-03/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-01-03/</guid><description>January Set 1
Derek and Montoya get into a fight on twitter Montoya is the leader of TEST, the biggest remaining Star Citizen Organization or something. At the time of this post, patreon displays that he recieves $388 a month from donors.
In light of the recent tragedy of an innocent man being killed after being doxxed and swatted, we as a community need to come together and condemn those who use doxxing as a means of intimidation!</description></item><item><title>December Set 15</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-01-02/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2018-01-02/</guid><description>December Set 15
Oh dear, Charlie Hall is taking a break from telling readers about how Star Citizen is leap-frogging Elite and actually describing his player experience with 3.0. It actually makes for good reading in places, though the deferential interjections seem tonally incongruent.
POLYGON: Star Citizen’s bugs will get you killed
So, i decided to watch the director commentary version.
&amp;lsquo;This is, you know, a more full version of the AI system we call subsumption,&amp;rsquo; says Chris showing people sitting on bunk beds.</description></item><item><title>December Set 14</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-12-31/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-12-31/</guid><description>December Set 14
Terrible decisions are a part of Chris Roberts history…
WHICH YOU CAN LEARN ABOUT IN THIS VIDEO WOOOOOOOOOOOOO
Worth Clicking: (video: Sunk Cost Galaxy - Chapter 2: The Mythological Roberts)
Used Car Rental Salesman chat
There&amp;rsquo;s a quite bit more to that story than what I mentioned, and it&amp;rsquo;s a lot more depressing and sad. And more than two sources have confirmed most of the details of that sad unspoken tale.</description></item><item><title>December mini Set 13</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-12-27/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-12-27/</guid><description>December mini-Set 13
Thankfully, you don&amp;rsquo;t have glitch in order to travel to this here youtube video…
Worth Clicking: (video: Sunk Cost Galaxy - Chapter 1: Past to Future to Present)
Unlike Chris, I actually write code for a living, and for many years applied that in the gaming industry. I have multiple AAA titles under my belt. You won’t believe any of that, same as you won’t believe that Star Citizen has already technologically failed.</description></item><item><title>December Set 12</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-12-26/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-12-26/</guid><description>December Set 12
Suck Cost Galaxy
Merry Christmas…
Worth Clicking: (video: Sunk Cost Galaxy - Overture)
Oh shit you forgot to check your stocking…
Worth Clicking: (video: Sunk Cost Galaxy - Foreword: The Reliable Narrator)
Chris on Spectrum
Chris has made a rare appearance on his weird discord knock-off in order to provide the base with some fresh talking points for the new year.</description></item><item><title>December Set 11</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-12-25/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-12-25/</guid><description>December Set 11
CIG airs their SQ42 video and label it a &amp;ldquo;verticle slice&amp;rdquo;
https://youtu.be/tpVzJiarjvc (video: 2 hours of mostly walking around)
https://youtu.be/qcHAfaQh3QE (video: Director&amp;rsquo;s Commentary)
It is pretty boring so here are some decent timestamps:
Timestamps:
Cafeteria Scene: timestamped youtube link (117)
Ser Davos gets shoved by the map: timestamped youtube link (725)
Crobberts rips off terminator joke: timestamped youtube link (982)
Encounter with mopman: timestamped youtube link (1058)</description></item><item><title>December Set 10</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-12-24/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-12-24/</guid><description>December Set 10
Holiday AtV is delayed 24 hours
CIG advertised their holiday show accross IGN and amoungst their fanbase. Only to cancel it 20 or 40mins before the scheduled time to go live.
CIG yanks the football away at the last second again.
I love you CIG, I really, really do.
What a trainwreck.
The hits keep on coming.
Imagine not beeing able to show gameplay of your game after five years of development</description></item><item><title>December Set 9</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-12-20/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-12-20/</guid><description>December Set 9
This encapsulates Star Citizen for me in a way I doubt the OP could ever understand or recognize. It&amp;rsquo;s got everything:
The pointless joke literally run into the ground as the only bit of content The huge, empty, ill-advised planet The wonky physics, with the Big Benny&amp;rsquo;s machine jittering all over the place The hilariously overwrought mocap of the guy doing his dumb victory dance The inability of commandos to affect change on anything (look at his feet in relation to the vending machine) It&amp;rsquo;s all just so perfect.</description></item><item><title>December Set 8</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-12-19/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-12-19/</guid><description>December Set 8
I&amp;rsquo;m about out of good faith for Chris. It&amp;rsquo;s been one hell of a wait. If they can&amp;rsquo;t resolve the garbage performance and start making leaps in development now that &amp;ldquo;the core of the game is there&amp;rdquo; I&amp;rsquo;m going to completely stop telling people about the game. Seriously tired of people giving me shit just because I&amp;rsquo;m excited for a game that has, so far, disappointed absolutely every single one of my friends, RL and online gaming friends.</description></item><item><title>December Set 7</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-12-18/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-12-18/</guid><description>December Set 7
I think the Coutts loan is a trivial detail in this story, and got blown out of proportion because some of the paperwork was public. Having to put up everything as collateral is a completely normal way to get a good deal on interest. Collateral and credit do not need to match in value, and in fact rarely do.
Amazon has an article linked on their AWS | Lumberyard page that includes quotes from Carl Jones talking about the switch.</description></item><item><title>December Set 6</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-12-17/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-12-17/</guid><description>December Set 6
CIG forked CryEngine 3.7 and modified it by over 50%.
Amazon forked CryEngine 3.8 and modified it by over 50%.
CIG rebased their branch onto Amazon&amp;rsquo;s branch of CryEngine.
Miraculously this took &amp;lsquo;a couple&amp;rsquo; of developers, &amp;lsquo;a couple&amp;rsquo; of days.
Of course this is how code works.
Welcome to Star Citizen.
did anyone make a joke about going from face over ip to case over ip?</description></item><item><title>December Set 5</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-12-15/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-12-15/</guid><description>December Set 5
Derek Smart **BREAKING** CryTek has followed through on its threat to sue RSI/CIG for a litany of things, and have hired one of the best law firms in the US. https://t.co/AawUMFZ8nT pic.twitter.com/Zm3QpSBoig
&amp;mdash; thedereksmart🕹️ (@dsmart) December 13, 2017 (tweet: CryTek has followed through on its threat to sue RSI/CIG for a litany of things, and have hired one of the best law firms in the US.</description></item><item><title>December Set 4</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-12-13/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-12-13/</guid><description>December Set 4
Worth Watching: (video: ship explodes buggedly)
THE NETCODE IS FINE THIS IS FINE
This is something I called in my July blog two years ago, when I stated the following: &amp;ldquo;a project with at least one insurmountable problem never passes zero percent completion, no matter how many other development goals are met.&amp;rdquo;
This is independent of Chris Roberts involvement being its own 100% guarantee of project failure.</description></item><item><title>December Set 3</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-12-11/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-12-11/</guid><description>December Set 3
I noticed that unrelated text subtitles flicker briefly onto the screen occasionally, as if the guy is continually in telepathic conversation with NPCs all over the &amp;lsquo;Verse. This isn&amp;rsquo;t the first 3.0 video where I&amp;rsquo;ve seen this phenomenon. Just a couple of instances below:
Someone in the verse is probably interacting with the shop at the same time, and this thing broadcasts every action of every player to every client regardless of range and sublevel.</description></item><item><title>December Set 2</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-12-10/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-12-10/</guid><description>December Set 2
$6.59M raked in for the sale.
My biggest problem, that I always have with SC, is that no matter how bad it is or how much I know I have to ignore logic, I keep assuming people are not fools.
All my projections are off because I can’t accept how stupid people are about this game.
It&amp;rsquo;s weird how square one is &amp;ldquo;these people are insane enough to spend thousands on jpegs of spaceships&amp;rdquo; and yet they still find new, inventive ways to come off as increasingly insane.</description></item><item><title>December 2017 set 1</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-12-05/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-12-05/</guid><description>December 2017 set 1
I don&amp;rsquo;t blame MoMA for not trying, though I disagree with the notion you could conceivably argue that the game&amp;rsquo;s development is in a good place right now in a way that would be even remotely convincing to any but the most blinkered of individuals. It&amp;rsquo;s fine to have faith in what&amp;rsquo;s being done (to a point), but even dismissing the arguments about the financials for CIG you can&amp;rsquo;t call what&amp;rsquo;s come out so far a positive sign of progress.</description></item><item><title>LAND SALES</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-12-01/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-12-01/</guid><description>November Set 10
I don&amp;rsquo;t have the time to go full , however I did want to really quickly jump on the dream. There are a lot of aspects to Chris&amp;rsquo; ramblings that I always thought would lose dreamers pretty quick. The best specific is the whole &amp;ldquo;arma&amp;rdquo; combat comparison he loves making. I always thought that the prospect of handing their adventure over into the hands of a 2 second ttk (in a game with hours of travel and busywork) that will almost certainly favor the kind of player that most SC fans are desperately attempting to escape would cause something of a riot and demand for a softer combat form.</description></item><item><title>November Set 9</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-11-28/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-11-28/</guid><description>November Set 9
Derek Smart 3.0 is such a shit-show, I don&amp;rsquo;t even want to write about it.
This is the end times.
i see a lot of tweets chock full of reasons why star citizen is great and still coming out and derek is the worst, but i don&amp;rsquo;t see a lot of cool star citizen gameplay videos
This has been The Star Citizen Paradox for a few years now.</description></item><item><title>November Set 8</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-11-26/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-11-26/</guid><description>November Set 8
I&amp;rsquo;ve managed to fit 8 deskeletonized children into one SCU. They are arranged facing out from the center (they each understand they are alone). The largest ones are in the corners. Some of them will die, but it&amp;rsquo;s normal so long as it doesn&amp;rsquo;t happen too soon into the journey because they are Meat. Place into the refrigerated portion of the Cargo Grid that will kill the rest of them because they are Meat.</description></item><item><title>November Set 7</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-11-25/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-11-25/</guid><description>November Set 7
3.0 Released to wave1
wave1 includes seemingly all the streamers, subscription holders, and many concierge members
Hello thread its time to wake up. 3.0 went public PTU.
So far all I&amp;rsquo;m seeing on reddit is &amp;ldquo;screenshot of ugly terrain OMG!&amp;rdquo; and guys… I&amp;rsquo;m starting to think that maybe, just maybe&amp;hellip; well maybe Star Citizen isn&amp;rsquo;t that good?
From the announcement:
&amp;ldquo;The goal of this initial PTU release is to increase our total player count in an effort test concurrency.</description></item><item><title>November Set 6</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-11-22/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-11-22/</guid><description>November Set 6
CIG probably going to sell virtual plots of land
https://robertsspaceindustries.com/comm-link/spectrum-dispatch/16270-Claiming-Space-The-Race-For-Land
Claiming Space: The Race for Land
blah blah blah blah
Recently, there has been a major push to encourage the settlement and development of the Empire’s frontier. As part of this initiative, the PDB has been making additional parcels of land accessible to the public for purchase. It is believed by policymakers that as sectors become more developed, they likewise become more secure.</description></item><item><title>November Set 5</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-11-21/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-11-21/</guid><description>November Set 5
To be honest… And I&amp;rsquo;m saying this as a first-round crowdfunding contributor who has been following this project since its conception in 2011&amp;hellip; You sound like someone in a cult. You&amp;rsquo;ve been promised so much, and there&amp;rsquo;s been so much hype, but all we have right now are a few tiny tech demos and a bunch of promises. This game was funded six years ago, has raised over $150 million, and still hasn&amp;rsquo;t been released, with no clear release date in sight.</description></item><item><title>Random Assortment</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-11-19/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-11-19/</guid><description>Random Assortment
god i&amp;rsquo;d rub anyone to read the amd letter
I have a p good feeling we will see the AMD letter by the end of 2018 or 2019
there&amp;rsquo;s some serious people sniffing around, and I don&amp;rsquo;t mean gaming sites n stuff
If the rings spin off due to collisions with player ships, that would be because the rings are created as physics objects (which makes them conserve momentum during collisions), and are configured with a preposterously small amount of mass relative to the ships.</description></item><item><title>Account Dissection</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-11-18/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-11-18/</guid><description>Account Dissection
I&amp;rsquo;m going to point out one error/mistake in the CIG accounts per day.
1.) Geography
In a consolidated set of accounts for a group of companies you eliminate intra-group transactions. This makes sense, because if you sell goods and services between two companies in a group you would just have matching revenue in one company and cost in the other. So in the CIG UK group, you can ignore the revenue in F42, this has an equal expense in CIG UK that you also ignore.</description></item><item><title>November Set 4</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-11-17/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-11-17/</guid><description>November Set 4
As I&amp;rsquo;ve pointed out before, back in January 2015, Roberts delivered a presentation in which he claimed that not only would the first episode of Squadron 42 be released by Fall 2015, but the full commercial release - meaning SQ42 and the persistent universe / MMO - would happen by the end of 2016. He made this claim at 1:32:06 in this video.
At the time of this presentation, the PU wasn&amp;rsquo;t yet in the alpha stage.</description></item><item><title>November Set 3</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-11-15/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-11-15/</guid><description>November Set 3
wrap up the r/ds meltdown real quick
&amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re not owned! We&amp;rsquo;re not owned!&amp;rdquo; the posters of r/ds shrieked as often and as loudly as possible before the enveloping silence…
&amp;ldquo;This doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean you won!&amp;rdquo; I sneer with my face pressed to the ground by Alexander&amp;rsquo;s sandal and illuminated by fires in Persepolis.
It&amp;rsquo;s one of my favorite parts of this whole thing.</description></item><item><title>November Set 2</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-11-12/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-11-12/</guid><description>November Set 2
https://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Employee-Review-Cloud-Imperium-Games-RVW17730194.htm
I worked at Cloud Imperium Games full-time (More than 3 years)
Pros
However this project and business turn out I&amp;rsquo;m happy I got to work on this once in a lifetime project that has really pushed boundaries in many areas of software development, games development, networking, and computer science.
Despite a lot of my ex-colleagues being younger, newer in the industry and sometimes inexperienced / naïve, they really worked incredibly hard and with huge amounts of enthusiasm, sometimes to the detriment of their own wellbeing and personal lives.</description></item><item><title>November Set 1</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-11-08/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-11-08/</guid><description>November Set 1
I think the best part of the Star Citizen Scam finally collapsing is that a large number of nerds will stop psychotically obsessing over Elite Dangerous being THE ENEMY and instead maybe shut up and enjoy the game that delivers on many of Chris Roberts promises.
I&amp;rsquo;m sure there will always be people that refuse to play it because it dared to exist opposite of Star Citizen and ten years from now at any mention of Elite Dangerous they will scoff and go into a rage filled tirade about &amp;ldquo;Polygon Tacos&amp;rdquo; or whatever but I think that will be a small minority.</description></item><item><title>October Set 5</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-10-31/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-10-31/</guid><description>October Set 5!?
So I&amp;rsquo;ve been a long time lurker but had to grit my teeth and pay up just to explain….well gloat on all you clowns,
Like how does it taste? The biggest event of the year where you guys were sourly clenching your fingers in anticipation of mocking something better than yourselves.
But Chris delivered. Showing Dereek Farts and you idiots what is possible in gaming.</description></item><item><title>Citizen Con 2017</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-10-29/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-10-29/</guid><description>CitizenCon 2017
Twitch recorded video:
Managers for 6 hours - https://www.twitch.tv/videos/185493179
Chris takes the stage - https://www.twitch.tv/videos/185578073?t=13m
It is all very boring dreams shilling.
Intel sponsors CitizenCon and Chris pushes their SSD : https://go.twitch.tv/videos/185493179?t=33m
i cant watch this shit it&amp;rsquo;s like QVC
Worth Clicking: https://clips.twitch.tv/RamshackleIronicChamoisTooSpicy
Disco Lando: &amp;ldquo;And this year of course we are fullfilling the CON in our CitizenCon&amp;rdquo;
holy shit twitch chat is wall to wall brutal as fuck</description></item><item><title>October Set 3 Run up to Citizen Con</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-10-22/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-10-22/</guid><description>October Set 3 - Run up to CitizenCon
In honor of the CitCon presentation that CIG has spent months preparing.
YOUTUBE: Chris Roberts talk about creating fake demos to trick Publishers into think you&amp;rsquo;re further along than you actually are…
Jared and Ben both have SA accounts, everything in SC has goons involved.
Let&amp;rsquo;s be real, almost every choice CIG has made at any given step during this has been the gooniest possible option.</description></item><item><title>All Time Greatest Posts</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-10-10/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-10-10/</guid><description>All Time Greatest Posts
Reserved for all time greatest posts
The one thing we should have learned by now is that time and Star Citizen makes fools of us all. The SC faithful have been so sure that total success is just around the corner for so long. And the SC skeptics have been so sure that total collapse has been just around the corner for so long.</description></item><item><title>October Set 2</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-10-08/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-10-08/</guid><description>October Set 2
I was just thinking today; if/when SC does go down, there&amp;rsquo;s going to be lots of unhappy backers who, despite their blind faith in the project, will still be looking for their &amp;lsquo;dream&amp;rsquo; game to be made. Any ideas on where they might turn to? Elite? the new X game? No Man&amp;rsquo;s Sky? Dual Universe? Beyond Good and Evil 2?
Hold on to your panties though because this is going to blow you away.</description></item><item><title>2017-10-06</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-10-06/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-10-06/</guid><description>Here, have an on-topic post:
Anyone who thinks Lando is some kind of bomb waiting to go off and spill the beans about CIG/Roberts is kidding themselves, you only need to watch some of the vids from Gamescon and you&amp;rsquo;ll see just how eagerly he talks complete bullshit in service of fleecing people for money. He outright makes shit up unprompted about what can be done in game, what&amp;rsquo;s in development, and what&amp;rsquo;s just around the corner.</description></item><item><title>September 2017</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-09-26/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-09-26/</guid><description>September 2017
Mocapping a few animations that end up blending into other animations is all fine and good, because its usually a brief second or two of animation that your anim team has to hand scrub anyway.
Mocapping an entire performance gets tricky. If you&amp;rsquo;re not 100% confident of the take, you can have a lot of problems. You get weird wandering heads, eye darting, jiggling jowls, hands and arms and legs clipping through clothes and backgrounds and other characters and a whole lotta other weird shit you gotta clean up by hand.</description></item><item><title>2017 August Set 1</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-08-10/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-08-10/</guid><description>2017 - August Set 1
&amp;ldquo;Soon there will be a jump gate that can take me to the Helios system! I bet we&amp;rsquo;ll have underwater vehicles by then and I can explore the vast depths of Helios II! I&amp;rsquo;m going to set up deep sea mining operations as soon as its live so I can get a head start carving out my thrilling future as an Oceanic Mining Tycoon!</description></item><item><title>January Set 5</title><link>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-01-10/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pricelesstrainwreck.github.io/post/2017-01-10/</guid><description>January Set 5
Streetroller points to the bleachers So Here&amp;rsquo;s The Deal: I&amp;rsquo;m suing Chris Roberts for consumer fraud in small claims court.
Everything he&amp;rsquo;s ever said will be used against him as a public figure, and his litany of LLC shell companies don&amp;rsquo;t protect him.
He either comes to Jersey to defend himself, or get&amp;rsquo;s a default judgment of being a fraud.
Fucking blow me.</description></item></channel></rss>